Guide to the John Eugene Unterecker Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series X: Other Manuscripts
  - Performance Poetry -- Performance at Kokee
  - Performance Poetry -- Reading April 17, 1985
  - Performance Poetry -- Windward College
  - Play ms. - Lysistrata
  - Poems -- Unterecker
  - Poems--Unterecker (Box 73)
  - Poems--Unterecker (Box 74)
  - Poems sent to George and Bob
  - Poetry Circulation Records
  - Poetry -- possible chapbook - uncollected poems
  - Poetry -- pre 1944
  - Poetry - "Wine" and "Collioure" poems
  - Preface for Shapiro's Ashbery
  - Prefaces--Conarroe's Berryman (Box 75)
  - Preface for Nelson's Bly
  - Preface for Kidder's Cummings
  - Preface for Ginsberg
  - Preface for Jemie book (2 folders)
  - Preface for Schlossberg's Imaginary Conversation with Einstein and Beckett
  - Preface for Orr's Kunitz
  - Preface for Rudman's Lowell
  - Preface for Moffett's Merrill
  - Preface for Quinn's Pound
  - Preface for Weston's Stevens
  - Prose (2 folders)
  - Reviews (misc.)
  - Reviews -- Columbia Press Contemporary Poetry Series Review
  - Reviews -- Dembo's Hart Crane's Sanskrit Charge
  - Reviews -- Dream of Alcestis, The
  - Reviews -- Frumkin reading
  - Reviews -- Frumkin, Gene -- Clouds and Red Earth
  - Reviews -- Harris: Coole Park and Ballylee
  - Reviews -- Hart's Bridge
  - Reviews -- American Way -- "Imagining Mind..."
  - Reviews -- Krupot -- Woodsmen or Thoreau and the Indians
  - Reviews -- Lohf, Lewis, Leibowitz, Voelcker
  - Reviews -- Martin -- With Friends Possessed
  - Reviews -- McPherson -- Singing With the Owls
  - Reviews -- Murphy -- Prodigal Father
  - Reviews -- Murphy -- Yeats
  - Reviews -- New Leader
  - Reviews -- New York Times Nature Poetry Roundup
  - Reviews -- Parkinson -- Crane/Winters correspondence
  - Reviews -- Poetry Hawaii
  - Reviews -- Schwartz -- Hart Crane: an Annotated Critical Bibliography
  - Reviews -- Shapiro -- Ashbery
  - Reviews -- Stewart -- The Open Water (Box 76)
  - Reviews -- Taylor -- Essays in Teaching
  - Reviews -- "Voices and Visions: Robert Frost"
  - Reviews -- Wood -- Bazaar
  - Statements -- Voyager
  - Text -- Goodbye Walls
  - Thomas, Dylan -- record cover piece
- Series XI: Subject Files
  - Acting (Box 76)
  - Applications
  - Automobile Receipts and warrants
  - Awards and prizes
  - Biography -- old and out of date
  - Christmas cards -- homemade
  - Christmas cards -- 1954
  - Christmas card material
  - Conferences
  - Contests -- poetry
  - Contracts -- book
  - Contracts and permission fees
  - Contracts -- teaching
  - Course descriptions
  - Current biography
  - Editorial -- Poetry Pilot
  - Editors
  - Education (Box 77)
  - Fellowships
  - France
  - Ghana
  - Grants -- ACLS -- 1972
  - Grants -- ACLS -- 1961, Guggenheim
  - Grants -- National Foundation Grant Applications
  - Hawaii -- Endangered species
  - Interviews
  - Kenya
  - Maps
  - Miscellaneous writings
  - Poetry publication record
  - Program notes
  - Publications sent to Roger Conover
  - Publication miscellany
  - Published prose -- annual lists
  - Star Bulletin paper (Box 78)
  - Texas -- maps and brochures
- Series XII: Transparencies
  - Yeats, Joyce
  - Beckett book
  - Drawings
  - Documents
  - Photographs
  - Printed Materials
  - Voyager (3 copies); August 22 (printed score); and a folder ofVoyager reviews. (Box 79)
  - Periodicals with contributions by Unterecker, A-Z (Box Boxes 80-88)
  - Periodicals, unsorted. (Box Boxes 89-91)
    [With contributions by Unterecker]
  - Books belonging to Unterecker (Box Boxes 92-96)